hawaiilife.com 2007-12-13

# Privacy Policy, HawaiiLife.com

Hawaiilife.com recognizes the importance of our client's privacy. This page describes how HawaiiLife.com handles information that we gather from people visiting the [www.hawaiilife.com](http://www.hawaiilife.com/) or contact us by mail, phone, or email. Any personally identifying information you provide to us is voluntary. We use this information to assist you based on a request you make – and for no other reason.

##### When you visit our Websites to compare and manage property:

We DO NOT use persistent cookies or tracking mechanisms that collect personally identifying information on our sites. Our Websites use session cookies to anonymously store properties saved in your “Real Favorites”. Session cookies are temporary files. We use these session cookies for site management purposes. Accepting sessions on our websites is voluntary; you may still use the site if you decline cookies.

##### If you choose to identify yourself when you call, write, email, or contact us through any process on our website:

### Information We Collect

We collect any personally identifying information, such as your name, street address, email address, and phone number, and any other information you provide to us.

### How We Use and Disclose Information

If you choose to provide personally identifying information to us, we will use and disclose it as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not provide your name or other identifying information, it may be impossible for us to refer, respond to, or assist you with your request. We may share your information with contractors acting on our behalf, such as call center operators and licensed real estate agents working with us, who are subject to confidentiality agreements.

  * If you contact us to request details on a property, we use the information you provide to fulfill your request or contact you about your request.
  * If you contact us to request assistance from a buyer’s broker, we use the information to fulfill your request or contact you about your request.

##### Here's what you should know about the security of the information you provide to us:

  * We use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to protect the transmission of the information you submit to us when you use our **secure online forms**. The information you provide to us is stored securely.
  * Email that you send us is not necessarily secure against interception. If your email communication includes sensitive information like your Social Security number, your bank account number, or your credit or charge card numbers, contact us through one of our secure online forms or by **mail or telephone**.
